<resources>
    <string name="app_name">shoeTrial</string>
    <string name="shoename1">Air Jooordan</string>
    <string name="reviewButton">Show Review</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="x_Dior_Air_Jordan_1">One of the most highly anticipated launches of the year. The Dior x Air Jordan 1 High sneakers are the first collaboration between the luxury powerhouse and sneaker giant. Crafted from wolf grey and sail white leather, these Air Jordan 1 High sneakers take on the iconic high-top silhouette, and update it by way of a grey Dior monogram swoosh logo. The perfect balance between classic and high-style.</string>
    <string name="Air_Jordan_13_Retro_1">Invest in a classic. Crafted from red and grey leather, these Air Jordan 13 Retro sneakers from Jordan are just what you need to make sure your sneaker collection is filled with the best. The perfect pick.</string>
    <string name="Air_Jordan_1_1">The trainer that started it the entire craze, the Jordan I was first released in 1985 and was worn during MJs first two seasons with the Chicago Bulls. This is one of the original colourways, reflecting the team colours of the Bulls, showcasing the multi-panelled construction of this now-iconic shoe. As well as being one of the very first ever athlete signature shoes, the Nike Jordan I was a masterpiece of marketing, with every detail, from the box and the iconic (wings) logo expertly considered.</string>
    <string name="Air_Jordan_1_Retro">Open your eyes to one of this year\'s most anticipated sneaker collaborations. Colombian singer J. Balvin, also known as "The Prince of Reggaton", has teamed up with Jordan to celebrate the Latinx community and music with a classic sneaker silhouette. Crafted from bold multicolour panels, these Air Jordan 1 Retro High J. Balvin "Colores y Vibras" sneakers pay true to Balvin\'s vibrant music and personality with this celebratory pair.</string>
    <string name="air2">Supplied by a premier sneaker marketplace dealing with unworn, already sold out, in demand rarities. Each product is rigorously inspected by experienced experts guaranteeing authenticity. Make sure your footwear is ready for the warm summer-time weather. Michael Jordan’s first signature shoe has been reimagined in a tropical-inspired green and blue tie-dye pattern.</string>
    <string name="air1">Supplied by a premier sneaker marketplace dealing with unworn, already sold out, in demand rarities. Each product is rigorously inspected by experienced experts guaranteeing authenticity. The Women’s Air Jordan 1 “Satin Black Toe” is a special construction of the original colorway of the Jordan 1 with satin paneling on the heel. Following the same blueprint of the “Satin Shattered Backboard” colorway that was also a women’s exclusive, this “Satin Black Toe” edition features a black and white leather upper with red satin at the heel.</string>
    <string name="air5">Supplied by a premier sneaker marketplace dealing with unworn, already sold out, in demand rarities. Each product is rigorously inspected by experienced experts guaranteeing authenticity. The Air Jordan 13 “Flint 2020” is the 2020 release of the beloved original colorway. Appearing alongside other original colorways in the late-90s, the “Flint” makeup is one of the most coveted looks of the Jordan 13 despite the fact that it does not employ the team uniform colors of the Chicago Bulls.</string>

</resources>